Guide to the Ray Stevens Ashbery papers, [1930-1971?].
Ashbery, Ray Stevens papers, [1930-1971?].
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Ray Stevens Ashbery papers, [1930-1971?].
3634
Ray Stevens Ashbery, 1902-1974
103 cubic ft.
Correspondence, subject files, constituent bills, reports, case files, estates, wills, and income tax files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, subject files, constituent bills, reports and case files of Raymond Ashbery from his tenure as New York State Assemblyman. Also, correspondence, case files, estates, wills, and income tax files from Ashberry's private law practice in Trumansburg, N.Y.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, subject files, constituent bills, reports and case files of Raymond Ashbery from his tenure as New York State Assemblyman. Also, correspondence, case files, estates, wills, and income tax files from Ashberry's private law practice in Trumansburg, N.Y.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Ashbery, Ray Stevens, 1902-1974.; New York (State). Legislature. Assembly.--Officials and employees.
Subjects:
Lawyers.; Politicians.
Places:
New York (State)--Politics and government.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Correspondence and other papers: access obtained with written permission of donor or heirs.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Personal papers, 1930-1964.
  Personal and law files, include papers related to Ashbery's private law practice, and businesses, i.e. "Film Libe" and real estate; also, "Ashbery for Assembly" campaign material.
  - RSA Law Miscellaneous Files, 1944-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - RSA Law Miscellaneous Files, 1941-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - RSA Law Miscellaneous Files, 1944-1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - RSA Law Miscellaneous Files, 1943-1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - RSA Law Miscellaneous Files, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Untitled, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Summer Session, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Robinson King, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ryan - Swartwood, Newton Auto Sales, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Manos - Income Tax, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Newman and Adams, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous - Collections, 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Untitled, 1948-1964 (Box 1, Folder 13-17)
  - Withholding and Social Security Reports, 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Tompkins Co. Bar 6th Judicial Convention, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bar Association Next Meeting, 1953-1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Hamilton - I.S.S., 1942-1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Income Taxes, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Untitled, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Estate of Isabella S. Scheid, 1932-1961 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Scheid Trust, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Scheid - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1941-1961 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Film Libe - Legal Manufacturing, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 27-28)
  - Turner-Freedman, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Real Estate, 1939-1941 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous, 1939-1947 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Unfiled Personal Correspondence, 1946-1952 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Unfiled Personal Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
  - Untitled, 1946-1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Income Tax - Trumansburg Realty Partnership, 1951-1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, 1930-1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Personal - R.S.A. 3-20-62, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, 1930-1963 (Box 2, Folder 8-May)
  - Radio Scroll, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Untitled, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 12-Oct)
  - Releases, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 13-16)
  - Untitled, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sheldon Court - U.S. Trust Company, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Windswept Bugle, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - AFA [Ashbery for Assembly] Speech Material, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Etna Speech, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Election - Town of Ulysses - District #1, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - AFA Petitions, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - A.F.A. Dryden Meeting - Oct. 15, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - AFA Political Ads, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - AFA League of Women Voters, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Republican County Committee and City, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Republican County Committee appointed Oct., n.d. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Speeches, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - AFA Radio Talks, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - AFA Biography and Photo, 1948-1954 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Notices - Republican Meetings, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - AFA Campaign, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - AFA Campaign Information on Other Candidates, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - AFA Notes of Congratulations, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - General Correspondence of Campaign, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - AFA Dewey - Warren Campaign, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Series II. Subject files, 1948-1962. Assembly files, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Alcoholics Anonymous, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - American Association Agricultural College Editors, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - AFA, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Ashbery - 1950 Campaign, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Ashbery Press Releases 1950, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Legislature Roster Tompkins Co. Assemblymen from 1818 to date, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Automobile Association, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Automobile Club, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bank of Groton - General '50, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Boorady, Norman, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Brown, Ben, 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Census, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Conservation, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Cornell, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Cornell - 1950, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Cornell - Meek, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - County Fair, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dickinson, C. L., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Drier, Donald, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Education, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Education - General Correspondence, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Education - Milmoe Bill, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Education - Regents, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Schools - Education, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Farm Bureau Federation, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Freedom Train, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Gasoline Tax - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Gasoline Tax - General, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Geer, William, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - George Junior Republic, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Groton, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Health, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Euthanasia - Health '50, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Pubic Health '50, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Highways, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Highway Maps, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Hines, Jack, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Insurance, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Kohn - General, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - League of Women Voters, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - League of Women Voters 1950, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Albany - Proposed Legislation, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Proposed Legislation 1950, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Legislative Index/Legislative Manual Requests, 1949-1952 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Library of State of New York, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Local finance - Taxes '50, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Meetings Attended, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Milk, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Morrison, Richard T., Sr., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Morse, Lewis, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Motor Vehicles, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Motor Vehicles, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Motor Vehicles - Trucks, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Oleo, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Official Compilation, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Optometry, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Palmer, E. L., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Palmer, Harold, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Pyle, Enos A., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Summary of Laws Affecting Real Estate, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Real Estate, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Red Book 1949-1950, 1950-1951, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Roberts, Ben, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Sampson College, ca. 1949 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Saperstone, David, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Assembly - Saratoga Trip - Republican State Convention, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Speech Material, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Speeches - Ithaca Schoolmasters, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Speeches Made, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Speeches to be Made, 1949, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - State Fair, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - State University, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - State University Bills (Meigs), 1951 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Sutton, Glenn N., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Taxes, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Taxes - General, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Health Center - Tompkins County, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Treman, Allan, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 79-80)
  - ACR-25. Steingut United World Federalists, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Van Orman, Ray, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Veterans, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Volunteer Fire Department, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Fire Districts - Brooktondale Firemen, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Welfare, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Wilkinson, Ernest, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Willard State Hospital, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Conservation - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Dog - Form Letter, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 91-93)
  - Oleo - Agriculture, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Oleo - Form Letters, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Oleo - Individuals, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 96-97)
  - Oleo - Manufacturers, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Oleo - Questionnaires, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Oleo - Resolutions, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Adams, Armand, 1946-1951 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Adams, B. A., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Assembly, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Assembly - Assistants, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Automobile Association - Ithaca, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bruce, Robert, J., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Brusch, Helmuth F., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Buyoucos, James, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cemeteries, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Churches, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Civil Service, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Colbert, J. Reed, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Comics, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Commerce and Industry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Conservation, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Conservation - New York State Conservation Council, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Conservation - Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Cornell - Inauguration of Deane W. Malott, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Legislative Dinner, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - County Laws, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Courts, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Dickerson, Charles, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Dickerson, Hungary Relief, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Disability Law, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Dykes, Charles E., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Education '51, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Education - General, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Education - General Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Education - Ithaca, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Education - Ithaca - Hayts Corners, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Education - Trumansburg, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Expense Accounts, 1950-1952 (Box 4, Folder 33-34)
  - Films, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Four H Club, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Friday Discussions, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Frommer, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Gasoline tax, 1951, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Geer, William C., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - George, Abe - Chacona, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - George Junior Republic - 1951, 1928-1951 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Hammond, Senator, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Health, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Highway, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Highways, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Highways - Trumansburg, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Housing, 194?-1950 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Ithaca Area School Study, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Ithaca Education, 1948-1951 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Ithaca Flying Service, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Ithaca Hospital, 1948-1950 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Ithaca Reconstruction Home, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Ithaca Supervisors Resolutions, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Ithaca Traffic, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Judiciary, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Legislation for 1951, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - License Plates, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - LoPinto, John, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Lueder, David A., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - McFall, Mrs. Pearl, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - McLean, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Meetings, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Morris, Evan J., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Motor Vehicle, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Motor Vehicle Committee, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Motor Vehicles - Special License Plate, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Panther Dam, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Passes, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Press Releases - 1951 Ithaca Journal, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Radio, 1050-1951 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Recommendations, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Regents, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Rent Control, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Republican Party - Ashbery - Tompkins County, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Republican Party - GOP (State), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Retirement, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Rumsey, Ellsworth, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - St. Lawrence Power, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Saranac Lake Trip, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Schaefer, Francis H. Jr., 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Scrapbook - RA, 1949-1952 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Severinghaus, Mrs. Jane, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Social Security, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - State University, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Sullivan, Louis W., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Supervisors, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Taxes, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Teacher Salaries, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Thruway, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Townley Motors, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Veterans, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Volunteer Firemen, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Wage Hour Law, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Welfare, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Willcox, Walter F., Reapportionment, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - World Government, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - A.A.A., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - AFA Acknowledgments to Signers, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - AFA Advertising, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - AFA Assembly, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - AFA Brochure, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - AFA Clippings, Newspaper, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - AFA Correspondence, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - AFA Financial, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - AFA General, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - AFA Mary and Clara Mailings, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - AFA Newspaper Stories, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - AFA Radio Talks, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Agriculture 1952, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Agriculture 1953-54, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Agriculture - North East Farm Foundation, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Amendments, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Assembly 1951 - Requests for Bills, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Assembly Floor, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Blue Laws 1952, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Budget, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Building Code 1952, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Building Code 1953, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Chamber of Commerce Ithaca Legislative Committee 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Chamber of Commerce - Empire State, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Chamber of Commerce - Empire State Legislative Summary, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Civil Defense, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Civil Service, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Comics, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Committees 1952, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Congratulations, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Conservation - Panther Dam 1953, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Cornell - Legislative Dinner 1952, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence - Congratulations, 1948-1952 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence - General re. Albany, 1948-1952 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence - General, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence - Invitations, 1949-1952 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - County Fairs, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Education, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 38-40)
  - Education - Ithaca Area 1952, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Education - Ithaca Study, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Education - Mentally Retarded Children, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Education - State University, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Education - Trumansburg 1953, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Eisenhower - Madison Square Garden - TV, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Grange League Federation - Conferences, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Hammond, Chauncey, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Health 1952, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Health - Tompkins County Hospital, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Highways - Good Roads, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 51-52)
  - Highways - Route 13, Naegley, F. K. 1952, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Highways - Thruway 1952, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Highways - Tompkins County, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 55-56)
  - Highways - Truck, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Howell, Mabel, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Insurance, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Ithaca Chamber of Commerce, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Ithaca, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Eugene, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Lansing, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Laws - 1949-51 Digest - Speaker's, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - League of Women Voters 1952, 1953, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
  - Legislative Manual 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Library - Lydia Sears, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Milk, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Miller, Lawrence E., 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - Monthly Economic Letter, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Motor Vehicles, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Motor Vehicles AAA, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Motor Vehicles Community Safety Organization, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Motor Vehicles - Frommer, 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Motor Vehicles - Inspection, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Motor Vehicles, Safety Council 1952, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Motor Vehicles, special License Plates, 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Motor Vehicles, Trucks 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Multiple Dwelling 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Narcotics - William Heimlich, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Passes 1952, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Pensions, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - PPR, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Dulton Peterson - Senator, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Press Releases, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Proposed Legislation, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 32-33)
  - Red Book 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Reapportionment 1952, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Rent Control, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Repper, Doric C., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Republican Party, County, Ithaca '52, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Republican Party, National, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Republican Party - National, 1953, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 41-42)
  - Republican Party - National 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Republican Party - National 1952, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Retirement, 1952, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - St. Lawrence Seaway, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Saranac Meeting - Bar Association, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Speech Material - O. Heck, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Speech Material Feb. 7, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Speech Material Oct. 17 on ..., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Stagg, Norman G. 1952, 1949-1951 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - State University, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Stillwell, Mrs. Margaret, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Supervisors, Tompkins Co. 1952, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Swartwood, Richard, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Tompkins County 1952, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Tompkins County Milk Producers, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Tompkins County Narcotics Council, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Tompkins County - Supervisors 1953, Resolution, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Tompkins County Taxpayer's Association, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Trailers and Camps, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Veterans 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Volunteer Firemen, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers 1952, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Welfare 1952, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Welfare, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Youth 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Ward 2, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Ward 6, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - A..A.U.W., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Agriculture, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture - Milk - Ithaca Area, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Airport, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Albany - Correspondence, week of Feb. 28, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Albany - Correspondence, week of Mar. 5, 1956, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Albany - Correspondence, Week of Mar. 8, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 10-Sep)
  - Albany - Week, Mar. 15 Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Albany - Filing Feb. 28, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Albany - Highway C Comission Meeting, Dec., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Amendments, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Amendments 1954-55, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Amendments - Voted on - Fall, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Ashbery - Campaign, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Ashbery - Campaign, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Assembly Campaign - W.H. C.U., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - RSA - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Ashbery - Republican Party, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Assembly - Week of Jan. 12, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Assessors Topics - Justice Court Topics, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Assessors Topics, 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Associated Industries, 1954, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Auburn Meeting - May 9-10 - Assemblymen, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Automobile Club - Finger Lakes, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Banks, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Banks - 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Bar Association, New York, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Bar Association - Tompkins County, 1951-1954 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Bar, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Bingo, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Bingo, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Building Code, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Business Women's Club Mar. 8, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Cayuga Lake - Freeman (Lighting), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Cerebral Palsy, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Empire State, 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Ithaca '55 State Affairs Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Legislative Report, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Charities, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Chatfield - Letters to the Editor, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Churches, 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Civil Defense 1957, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Clippings, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Civil Service, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Clark, Thaddeus, 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Comic Books, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Compulsory Insurance, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Conservation, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Constance Cook Memoranda, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Corning, Sept. 28 meeting, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Corporation Law, 1954, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, General, 1951-1953 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, General, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Cortland County Women's Republican Club, 1957, 1953-1957 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Courts, 1955, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Courts, 1956, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Courts, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Courts, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 63)